(Howard:)that makes it kind of hard
to face her now.
(Leonard:)That covers anything
from farting in bed
(Leonard:)to killing a homeless guy.
(Leonard:)Oh, my God.
(Leonard:)You ran over a hobo.
(Howard:)No. Stop asking.
(Leonard:)All right, fine. So you want to
get back together with her,
(Leonard:)but you're too
ashamed to face her
(Leonard:)because of whatever
it is you did.
(Howard:)In a nutshell.
Okay.
(Leonard:)Well, how about this?
(Leonard:)Kidnap Bernadette from the opera
(Leonard:)wearing a creepy mask so
she doesn't know it's you.
(Howard:)Now, you see, I don't know
if you're kidding or not.
(Raj:)You're being
unreasonable.
(Raj:)Why can't
I have a desk?!
(Sheldon:)Our collaboration is a work
of the mind.
(Sheldon:)We don't need desks.
(Raj:)You have a desk.
(Sheldon:)Correct.
But I can't have one.
(Sheldon:)You're two for two.
(Leonard:)Why can't he have a desk,
Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)Oh, Lord, will
this day never end?
(Sheldon:)As I've explained repeatedly
to Dr. Koothrappali,
(Sheldon:)whose ability to comprehend
the American idiom fails him
(Sheldon:)when it's convenient,
(Sheldon:)there's absolutely
no money
(Sheldon:)in my budget for
additional office furniture.